MUSIC BLARES, SHE RAPS
CROWD CHEERS
DANCE MUSIC THUMPS
THEY CHEER
Respect!
ENGINE REVS
GUNSHOT, PANICKED CLAMOUR
Demir! Demir!
Demir, stay with me!
Call an ambulance!
Anybody, help!
Demir, stay with me!
SHIP HORN BLOWS
Go on.
You know this?
This is poetry from pressed olives.
Mm-hm.
And?
It's really good.
THEY LAUGH
I can't wait for you
to see it, all of it.
I'd like to take you to
our heritage olive groves,
and I will really
teach you the business.
Like, bring you in.
You realise I already have a career?
I know.
I always knew you would excel
in anything you do and...
Yeah?
How would you know that?
The label - you recognise it?
You drew it,
when you were six years old.
A couple of weeks before
your mother took you away.
So, where were you?
Hmm?
The last 20 years?
Mehmet...
..that wasn't only my fault.
Your mother made it impossible...
She was sick, Dad.
I failed you both.
I've made mistakes, I know that.
But all I want now is to try and...
..and do whatever I can
to make it right.
Give me a chance.
That's all I'm asking for.
PHONE BUZZES
Yeah?
PHONE: Sir, are you available?
Yeah. No, no, no.
No, I'll be right there, yeah.
Got to go.
Sorry.
No worries.
Uh, thank you for, uh...this.
I'll see you. Yeah.
SIRENS WAIL
I thought this was a shooting.
That was inside the venue.
And that was the shooter.
Had misfortune as he
tried to get away.
And the victim was
Erol Karagul's son.
Erol Karagul?
Is that someone important?
PHONE BUZZES
Oh, ten points to Hufflepuff.
This just came from the hospital.
That's the shooter.
Just a boy.
You know I'm a Gryffindor,
though, right?
Hufflepuff...
TEARFULLY: Demir and Eylo
were fighting, and then...
..this guy just
comes out of nowhere.
Take your time.
This was Demir's big night.
He really believed in this
new kid. He was so excited.
Mrs Karagul, we will find
exactly who was behind
your husband's murder.
Excuse my colleague.
He's still new to the city.
Mrs Karagul is the
Demir's father's wife.
Erol Karagul.
Was he here tonight?
No.
At least he was spared that.
But as Detective Suleyman says,
we'll do everything we possibly can
to get to the bottom of
this appalling tragedy.
Thank you.
If Eylo did hire the shooter, it's
a ballsy move to be there for it.
Ballsy, or just really stupid?
You know, why place yourself at the
scene of a hit that you planned?
Maybe he wanted to watch him die.
Yeah, no, I don't buy it.
Beneath all the macho crap,
Eylo is a talented artist.
He's a performer.
I'm sure you two can continue
this debate
as you look for Eylo together.
I very much want to
question him in the morning.
OK.
Well, where are you going?
Ah.
I have a wife at home who's
extremely tired of being pregnant.
So, I only know two natural ways
of inducing a birth.
But, unfortunately...
..Fatma doesn't like spicy food.
So, duty calls.
PHONE BUZZES
Yeah?
PHONE: Sir, are you available?
Where are you...
..going. Yeah?
THEY CHATTER
VIDEO GAME BEEPS
THEY CHUCKLE
DOOR SHUTS
BEKIR GROANS
Uh-huh.
PHONE RINGS
Ah, the dynamic duo.
I trust you have good news.
After spending all night searching
every recording studio, bar,
nightclub and member's
club in Istanbul...
Yeah, he walked right
into the station.
I'm on my way. See you.
HE CHUCKLES
It seems you led my
officers a merry dance.
I heard you had half the police
department looking for me, so...
..I thought I'd do you a favour.
Why did you flee the crime scene,
then? I freaked out.
There was blood everywhere.
I just needed to get my head
together. And find out a way to
explain your argument with Demir
seconds before he was killed.
It wasn't a real argument.
It was an act.
So you're saying you were just
pretending to hate each other?
Demir came up with it.
It was clicks.
I mean, likes, retweets.
He wanted to use it to launch Hevi.
Look, he sent me an email yesterday.
Basically wrote a script for it.
"Make sure you're in my face
at the after show.
"Talk crap about Hevi.
"Don't punch me, like last time."
My son showed me
something this morning.
Now, that's you and Demir there,
and various other associates.
Now, the boy on the far left...
Yeah, that one.
Who's that?
That's Muzo.
He killed Demir.
He what?
Muzo killed Demir?
Why?
I was hoping you
could help me with that.
He's, uh, one of those
kids who just wants rep.
A name. I mean, they'll
smoke, fight, do anything.
Did have a relationship with Demir?
Well...
There's always kids
like that around,
and Demir tried to protect them.
He knew where he came from.
The money, the privilege...
..he always tried to
spread it around a little.
So, perhaps Muzo
killed Demir for rep?
Can you think of anybody else
who may have wanted Demir dead?
I don't know.
Really. But...
Like, his family is messed up.
You know what crazy
rich people are like.
Demir's father, Erol Karagul.
Built the textile factories
he inherited from his father
into a garment manufacturer for
the biggest international brands.
What are we talking, money-wise?
Hard to say, but millions.
Erol has always been super
discreet about the true extent
of their wealth.
Not all they are
quiet about, either.
Erol was very private before
his marriage to Faith Irving,
an American fashion model.
What about Demir's mother?
His mother died in childbirth,
along with their second child.
Well, we'll have
to uncover what we can.
You two follow up on the shooter.
We do have a known address, yes?
Yes.
Muzaffer Altun. He has a parole
listing to an apartment in Esenler,
rented by his uncle, Senol Tekin.
And you?
I'm going to have to slum it.
Boss.
I'll send you the address.
Cem Kartal.
DOOR OPENS
Cem! Cem!
I don't need you to tell me
how to do this.
I get it!
Right, then let me deal with it
the way I want.
I'm just looking out for you!
Dillon, let it go.
Cem, would you tell her to stop?
Faith!
Seriously, this funeral
is not your responsibility.
That man is my responsibility.
Faith.
Let us take care of the
arrangements, please.
We have to get this right, Cem.
We will.
Inspector. Mrs Karagul.
I was wondering, may
I speak to Mr Karagul, please?
Uh, yeah.
He's just finishing a meeting
with his PA. But I'll walk you up.
Thank you.
Firstly, may I say what
a terrible burden it must be
having this funeral thrust upon you.
For you and the whole
Karagul family, I'm so sorry.
It must be a comfort to
have your brother here.
I'm going to the pool.
Is it just fortunate timing,
or does he live here with you?
He's just visiting from the States.
He's here on business.
Right. What business is he in?
Finance, mostly.
Actually, he was working
on something with Demir.
Erm, a new streaming platform
for the Turkish diaspora
in US and Europe.
But, erm, yeah...
Is he or she your first?
Yeah.
She.
And hopefully not my last.
My wife is pregnant too,
and it's a girl.
Our fourth, and most
hopefully the last.
THEY LAUGH
You can take a seat.
Thank you.
Your brother was right, you know.
You have to take care of yourself.
You are the light in
the darkest of times.
"Do not go gentle
into that good night."
HISSING AIR
MONITOR BEEPS
Huh.
New phone. Burner?
Sure. Yeah.
Hey.
Wow. Not even trying to hide it.
No.
So this was a paid hit.
And the first thing he did was
buy the bike he used to do it.
Business expense.
That's not funny.
My brother is the same age.
You have a little brother?
Uh, yeah.
Anyway, let's see what else we can
find and get back to the station.
IKMEN: Muzaffer Altun.
Do you know him?
No.
I have no idea who this is.
Or why he would want to kill my son.
Oh.
I never had much time
for his music business.
Couldn't understand
his passion for it.
That hurt him, I think.
I should have been there for him.
Maybe then I could have
made sense of all this.
This is what I'm here for.
I understand there was
a fight at the club.
Yes. But, uh, what about here?
Was there a rupture in the family?
Inspector.
Oh, of course.
Sorry.
You have marvellous taste.
Extraordinary library and, uh...
..wonderful house.
No compensation for
the loss of a son.
No. You're right.
You know, my wife is about
to give birth very soon.
Most nights, I lay awake thinking,
"I'm not going to cope.
I'm an old man.
"Too old to have a new baby."
But then, morning comes...
..and you face the day.
You do.
You didn't answer my question, sir.
Were there any ruptures
in the family?
No.
My son was loved...
..by everyone.
Everything points to Muzo
being hired to kill Demir.
The cash, burner phone,
motorbike he bought.
And the phone?
Muzo's phone only ever
received one phone call,
from an unregistered number.
Another burner?
Exactly.
And the cell tower data puts
the location of that call
within this one-mile radius,
which just happens to have...
The Karagul house in it. Yes.
So, someone in that house
wanted Demir dead.
It must be about
the Karagul fortune.
Demir, he was the main heir.
Especially considering
Erol Karagul is extremely sick.
I saw blood marks on his wrist
consistent with blood cancer.
So, back there tomorrow, right?
The day of Demir's funeral?
Yeah, no sense in idling.
Go home, get some rest.
We'll go there fresh tomorrow.
Good work today.
Thank you, sir.
Good. Goodnight.
Night. Goodnight.
So, would you like a ride home?
Uh, yeah.
Well, thank you for the lift.
Yeah, no problem.
It's on my way home.
Good day. Yeah.
Good two days.
Yeah, right?
See you tomorrow.
You too.
LINE RINGS
Oh...
HE COUGHS
Thank you for doing this,
by the way.
You helped me find out
what's happened to Gozde.
I owe you.
But I've been down every
rat hole in the city.
No-one knows Kayra Khan.
Are you sure it's a name?
Whatever it is,
it's worth killing for.
And what did Leyla's friend say
when you asked about the case?
Told me to leave it alone.
But love makes you do crazy things,
right?
Yeah.
So if we're trying to help Leyla,
what are we doing here?
We're here to see the king
of the rats.
MUSIC PLAYS
Yeah, don't worry.
I'm not here to arrest you.
Just want to talk.
Kayra Khan.
Who is he?
HE CHUCKLES
Huh?
PHONE BUZZES
TV SPORTS COMMENTARY PLAYS
Dad.
Mehmet.
So good to see you last night.
Uh, yeah.
So, we're all going down
to the summer house
in Ayvalik next weekend.
I'd love you to come
and meet the family.
Uh...
Yeah, well, erm...
This case I'm working on, it's...
..it's complicated.
OK, I get it.
No problem.
So, how is the Karagul case going?
Uh, why would you know about that?
Well, it's such an important case.
I assumed everybody was on it.
You do know about
the rumour, don't you?
About the Karagul fortune,
how it all started?
No.
Families like these,
old Istanbul blue bloods,
they act like they're old money.
Ottoman royalty.
People coming from the countryside
or, God forbid,
immigrants like me...
Dad, what's...what's the rumour?
Well, supposedly,
it all started with the house
they still live in now...
It originally belonged to the best
friend of Erol Karagul's father,
a Greek guy, and during
WWII, he asks Erol's father
to shelter his estate in the
Karagul name, protect it.
But after the war...
He never gave it back?
Erol's father never gave it back.
Figures.
Interesting.
Yet more intrigue around
the Karagul dynasty.
I traced the cash
from Muzo's sneaker box
into an auction house in Akaretler.
Suleyman, pay the
auction house a visit.
See if this cash leads anywhere.
In the meantime,
Ayse and I will try and find out
who made that call to Muzo.
All right.
Did you do anything fun last night?
No.
Just flopped out on the sofa.
Didn't even bother to eat.
OK.
Good luck. You too.
Welcome to Guzelbahce auction house.
How can I help you?
Detective Suleyman. I have
an appointment at 12:00.
I'll let her know you're here.
Detective Suleyman.
I can confirm that the
money did come from us.
OK.
I've just spoken to our bank,
and they've traced
the serial numbers.
The cash you are talking about was
taken out for our auctions on...
..22nd of March.
Four weeks ago.
Can you trace the exact
transaction that was used in?
Not unless you know what item
the person in question sold
in order to get the cash.
That cash was used to
fund an assassination.
Sometimes our clients
wish for their transactions
to be conducted in cash.
There's nothing illegal about it.
Do you have CCTV
footage of that day?
Yes, we do.
I'm going to need that sent over
as soon as possible, please.
Of course.
DOOR OPENS
Cem Bey...
Still, you haven't
done what I asked!
But I-I...
I'm sick of your excuses!
When I speak,
it's not a request.
Yes, sir.
Apologies.
Oh, it's quite all right.
Although, I don't know
why you keep bothering us.
You should be talking to the
psycho that actually shot Demir.
Well, because he's dead.
When did you find out Erol was ill?
He is very ill, isn't he?
Blood cancer, leukaemia.
I saw the marks on his wrist.
Stage three. Hmm.
It's very aggressive.
Honestly, I...
I just wish Demir
had stepped up sooner.
Taken some of the responsibility
so that Erol could focus on
his health and his family.
I mean, that's what
he did for his father.
I just want him to have
more time with our daughter.
Of course.
But whatever happens,
she'll be amply provided for.
What are you implying?
What, you think I married
a dying old man for a pay-out?
Jesus.
Why don't you check
the medical records?
We were married
before his diagnosis.
Your brother, Dillon, he was going
into business with Demir, wasn't he?
And it mustn't have
been without stress.
It was going great.
Huh...
Well, it's peculiar,
because yesterday you told me
he was visiting -
but according to Cem
he has been visiting
for over a year now.
So?
Mm...
You haven't been married long.
Was there strain on the family
to bring in your little brother
to live with you so quickly?
Not really. It's a big house.
Yes, it is a big house.
What about Demir?
What did you think of him?
My God...
You're incredible.
I love Erol Karagul.
And when you love a man,
you love his family.
Faith.
We're supposed to wear these.
Come on.
Let's go. I want to get there early.
Inspector.
We have a funeral to attend.
Oh, yes, of course.
Tell me, Lina, what is Cem like
to work for?
SIGHING: Oh...
Cem can be...a little harsh
sometimes with the staff.
He's just under a lot of stress,
that's all.
And, honestly...this family
really needs someone like him.
Cem's the glue
holding them all together.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry. It's not my place.
Lina.
They fought.
A lot.
Erol and Demir?
Not Erol.
PHONE RINGS
Ayse.
Oh.
HE HUMS QUIETLY
LAMP RATTLES AND RINGS
What's our plan here?
You go left, I go right,
Ayse at the back.
But we tread lightly.
I'll never hear the end of it
if we don't.
MOURNERS SOB AND SNIFF
CLERIC RECITES RITES
DISTANT SIRENS
I've got a visual.
CROWD RESPONDS TO RITES
IMAM: Allahu Akbar.
Allahu Akbar.
Assalamualaikum warahmatullah.
EROL SOBS
Erol, Erol...
Let me, please. Let me.
Ayse, do you have a visual?
Negative.
Police, police.
KEYPAD BEEPS
Taxi!
Bus station, please.
DRIVER: Where you catch bus to?
Many bus station in Istanbul.
Bulgaria.
Like, now!
DOORS LOCK
Well, hope you don't mind
if we ask you a few questions first.
# Estetik surgery yaptim abi
# Erkeklerle gezdim abi
# Bu mevsim benim mevsim abi
# Bi' kadeh bana ne yapti abi?
# Bi' kadeh sana ne yapar abi?
# Soylediler bana kizlar abi
# Ha bu olaya gelince abi
# Ha-ha, sorry!
# Isler nasil? Isler normal
# Benim mod hep hep anormal
# Go crazy, go stupid anormal
# Sen normal, ah, ben anormal
# Isler nasil? Isler normal
# Benim mod hep hep anormal
# Go crazy, go stupid anormal
# Sen normal, ah, ben anormal
# Ona location
attim yarim saate bende
# Yarin kahvaltiya kahvemi
alirim sade
# Alize, a ne Alizade
# Five million benim simdi elde
# Rich bitch iyi benim keyfim
# Moscow-Istanbul benim seklim
# Big dick! O benim prensim
# Bitch pembe benim rengim
# Pirlanta yuzuk
hep parmagimda da da
# Yuz defalarca soyledim evet
da da da
# Fake lo-lo-love hep bos sevda
# Hep soylerler, "Kak dela detka?"
# Isler nasil? Isler normal
# Benim mod hep hep anormal
# Go crazy, go stupid anormal
# Sen normal, ah, ben anormal
# Isler nasil? Isler normal
# Benim mod hep hep anormal... #